directmatches.com 2007-12-31

# DirectMATCHES :: Site

**Directmatches.com Privacy Policy**  
Effective on: (11/04/05)

Welcome to Directmatches.com. Your privacy is important to us. To understand our privacy policy, please read this notice explaining our online information practices. This Privacy Policy describes how Directmatches.com treats information received about you when you become a member or when you otherwise provide information to us. 

**Registration on Directmatches.com**  
When you register, we ask you to provide your name, postal address, and e-mail address. This is necessary in order collect online payments for billing purposes, also to be able to send you rebate checks for rebates earned through our eRewards program, or distributor commission checks, provide customer service and, to improve our service making it more convenient for you. 

There are eight different member types. Each member type collects different information in order to provide the match making service. Business members, for example, will be asked questions about their type of occupation, business topics they enjoy and business interests. Romance members will be asked questions about their appearance, age group, and life style. Pen Pal members will be asked questions about what you are looking for in a pen pal relationship, how often you'd like to correspond, and what topics of discussion are of interest to you. Job seekers are asked to select a job category and post a resume. Employers are asked to provide company information and select which position categories they are seeking to hire. Models are requested to provide information on their appearance and experience. Agents are required to post their company information. All the information collected is used for managing the features of the service. 

Directmatches.com uses Independent Representatives as a means to market its service to the market place. When you register on the site your email address and phone number will be made available to the Independent Representative that referred you to the site in his or hers report. The Independent Representative may contact you at any time to provide you with information about the service, answer questions, and provide support or other types of contact. 

**How We Use Member Information**   
Besides using your personal information for billing purposes, we use your email address to send you member matches via email and news about the company. Other members do not have access to your personal email address, unless you provided it to them directly. Our eRewards program is a complementary online shopping program where you can earn rebates for shopping online through Directmatches.com when you register. We also use your information here to track your purchase transaction requests and fulfillment of any goods purchased online in order to send your rebates earned through eRewards. This is to ensure that your account is properly credited and to better combine services and improve content and navigation. Finally, we may use the information to send you e-mail notifications about, new site features, and to alert you to new products, services and special offers. This contact is done directly by Directmatches.com but can contain information directly about our affiliate’s special offers or promotions or other marketing material. 

If you choose to use our Tell-A-Friend feature, our member match referral service to tell a friend about another member’s profile you found on our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the member’s profile you’ve sent. Directmatches.com does not store this information and the information is for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

**Who Sees Member Information**  
A small number of Directmatches.com employees or contracted consultants or parties may have access to your personal information. We may use other services, contractors or vendors to provide some of the services for example credit card and payment processing, technical services, development or repair. If we need to disclose personal information for them to provide the services, it is with the requirement that the information is kept confidential and is used only for those services. 

For your protection we also use specialized third party credit card processors and payment systems in order to facilitate payments. When you enter your billing credit card details it is on a third party site and not directly on Directmatches.com even though the page may contain the Directmatches.com logo or look and feel. This is done to keep a flow to our existing pages and for technical sequence of navigation. 

Directmatches.com will disclose our Member Information in cases where, in its discretion, it deems such disclosure is required or appropriate in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

In the event Directmatches.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email or we may post a notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Our Security Precautions**  
The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored on limited-access servers. Our [host](http://www.interland.com/) operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems to guard the integrity and privacy of your personally identifiable information. 

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Contact with Directmatches.com**  
At no time will Directmatches.com ask for your username, password or personal information in an unsolicited phone call, e-mail or letter. Contact us by using this form if you receive such unsolicited communication. 

**Children**  
You must be eighteen or over to register as a member of Directmatches.com or use the Website. Membership in the Service is void where prohibited. In using our services, you represent that you are at least 18 years of age. 

**Other Sites and Links**   
Our sites contain links to other sites whose policies and practices may be different than ours. Members should review other sites' privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

**Cookies**   
The use of cookies is common throughout the Internet. Like many Websites, our Site uses cookies to keep track of your purchases and other activity on the Site and enhance your experience. We also use cookies to, track session time, deliver content, save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal and financial information so you do not have to reenter it each time you visit the Site. Directmatches requires its members to have cookies turned on in order to accumulate rebates, because most sites with which you will be shopping through require cookies. These cookies are not tied to your personally identifiable information. 

**Chat Rooms, Message Boards, Forums and Live Help**   
Warning - Disclosing personally identifiable information online through Chat Rooms, Forums, and Message Boards makes the information submitted public information; such disclosure may increase your chance of receiving “spam” or unsolicited email or other unwanted communication or contact. Please be extremely cautious and use careful discretion when disclosing any personal information online or through email. Directmatches.com is not responsible nor controls the information you provide. 

Our Live Help technology is owned by Directmatches.com therefore; information submitted here is not shared with other third parties. The communication is a one-on-one chat function with an employee of Directmatches to help with issues or questions you have about the site or service. The messages you post here are not seen by other members. 

**Member Corrections and Personal Information Updates**  
It is your responsibility to maintain accurate contact information, modify personal information or demographic information you have provided to us. If you need to make changes at any time, you can visit your edit profile on your account. The information stored on this page is our only means of reaching you. Please beware that it may take a few hours for our servers to update your information change. Directmatches.com is not responsible for, information, rebate checks or other matters that are sent to incorrect addresses when the address in question is the one listed in that member's account at the time the material was issued. 

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our registration form. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us by using this form. When you login to our site we offer you an opportunity at any time to opt-out of certain communications on your edit account page. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. 

**Delete or Deactivate account**  
If you have reason to believe that your account is no longer secure, you may delete your profile by contacting us on this form. You can set up an entire new account with a new username and password. 

**Policy Modifications**   
If at any point we decide to use particular personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email or by providing notice on this page. Please note we reserve the right and may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check this page periodically. 

**Acceptance of these Terms**  
By using our web site and services, you signify your consent to Directmatches.com's Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Directmatches.com Web sites or services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Please review this page regularly when you visit the site. 

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about the Directmatches.com policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us by using this form. 

Or mail to:   
DirectMatches Corp   
Attn: Customer Care  
1654 Plaza America Drive # 335  
Reston, VA 20190-4700 

Or call: 1-800-287-2162
